Coffee.
咖啡
-Thank you. -Cappuccino.
-謝謝 -卡布其諾
And a nice,hot cider for Monica.
摩妮卡的熱蘋果酒
Thank you.
謝謝
Rach,why does my cinnamon stick have an eraser?
瑞秋,為何我的肉桂棒上有橡皮擦?
That's why.
這就是原因,
Sorry.
對不起
The One With The Stoned Guy
六人行 第1季 第15集 大麻客
-=BT之家DRM小組 http://bbs.btbbt.com=- 榮譽出品 河馬根據網絡字幕微調製作
Chandler?
錢德
Miss Tedlock,you look lovely today.
泰洛克小姐,你今天真漂亮
That is a very flattering sleeve length on you.
我能說這件衣服真好看嗎?
Mr. Costilick would like you to stop by his office today.
科斯特.力克先生希望你在下班後 能到他辦公室去
If it's about those prank memos, I wasn't involved.
如果他是為搞笑備忘錄 不是我幹的,
Nothing at all. Really.
和我完全沒有關係.真的.
And frankly,those shenanigans have no place in an office environment.
弗蘭克,辦公室裡沒有地方容納這些惡作劇.
Hey,you guys!
各位,
Chandler's coming and he has incredible news.
錢德說他有天大的好消息
So when he gets here, let's all act,like,you know
所以他來的時候我們就……
Never mind. But it was gonna be really good.
不管了,這一定很有意思.
What's going on?
到底怎麼了…
So it's a typical day at work...
今天和平常沒什麼兩樣
...and Big Al tells me he wants to make me processing supervisor.
然後艾爾叫我到他辦公室 說他要我當電腦處理的主管
-That is great! -Congratulations!
-真是太好了 -恭喜...
So I quit.
所以我就辭職不幹了
Why?
為什麼?
Why? This was a temp job.
為什麼?因為這只是暫時的工作
Chandler,you've been there for five years.
錢德,你已在公司五年了
I know,but if I took it,I'd be admitting that this is what I do.
我知道,但接受升職 不就承認這就是我的目的
Does that mean we have to start buying our own toilet paper?
這是不是意味著我們必須開始自己購買手紙
That was Joey Tribbiani with the big picture. Dan?
那是有大照片的喬伊.丹?
Was it more money?
這那不是能賺更多錢?
Doesn't matter. I just don't want to be a guy who sits in his office...
我不在乎,我不想成為 坐在辦公室到午夜
...worrying about the WENUS.
擔心"WEENUS"的人
The "WENUS"?
"WENUS"?
Weekly estimated net usage system. It's a processing term.
"每週估計淨值使用系統" 這是電腦處理的術語
Oh,that WENUS.
哦，那個是"WENUS"啊
What will you do?
你有何打算?
I don't know. But I won't figure it out working there.
我也不知道該怎麼辦 我只知道我不會再待在那兒工作了
I have something you can do!
我有一份你可以做的工作
I have this new massage client,Steve.
我的新按摩客戶史蒂芬
Anyway,he's opening up a restaurant...
他開了一家餐廳
...and he's looking for a head chef.
他正在尋找總廚師
-Hi,there. -Hi.
-你好 -你好.
I know. You're a chef and I thought of you first.
我知道你是個廚師,而且我先想到你
But Chandler's the one who needs a job right now,so....
但錢德目前沒有工作所以...
I just don't have a lot of chef-ing experience.
我沒有太多廚師的經驗
Unless it's an all-toast restaurant.
除非那是一家只賣土司的餐廳
What is he looking for?
他想要什麼菜色?
He wants to do something eclectic.
他想要菜色豐富多變
He's looking for someone who can create the entire menu.
因此他在找一個能創造出整個菜單的人
So,what do you think?
意下如何?
Thanks. I just don't see myself in a big,white hat.
謝了.我大概沒資格戴白色大帽吧(無法勝任)
Oh,Monica! Guess what?
摩妮卡,考慮考慮?
a perfect run-up and there he goes,a perfect....
一個完美的積累,然後就自然而然出現了,完美的
Watch stuff like this...
看看這個
...and you realize why evolution is just a theory.
你就知道為什麼變革僅僅是理論上的事情了.
Can you see my nipples through this shirt?
你能透過襯衫看見我的乳頭嗎?
No,but don't worry. I'm sure they're still there.
看不見,但別擔心,它們還在
Where are you going?
你要上哪兒去,西裝筆挺先生?
I have an appointment with Dr. Robert Pilman,career counselor-a-go-go!
我和羅伯提曼博士有約,求職顧問阿哥哥
-I added the "a-go-go." -Career counselor?
-阿哥哥是我加的 -求職顧問?
You guys all know what you want to do.
你們都已找到人生的方向
I don't.
還沒
You guys in the living room all know what you want to do.
在客廳裡的各位 全都知道未來該怎麼走
You have goals. You have dreams. I don't have a dream!
你們有目標,有夢想, 但我卻沒有夢想
The lesser-known "I Don't Have a Dream" speech.
少見的「我沒有夢想」演說
I love my life! I love my life!
我愛我的人生!我愛我的人生!
"Brian's Song"!
布萊恩的歌
-The meeting went great? -So great!
-見面的結果如何? -相當順利
He showed me where the restaurant's gonna be.
他告訴我未來餐廳的位置
It's not too big or too small. It's just right.
就在第十街不太大也不太小, 大小適中
Was it formerly owned by a blond woman and some bears?
前任老闆是金髮女人和幾隻熊嗎?
I'm cooking for him Monday, kind of an audition.
週一我們要煮一餐讓他品嚐 有點像是面試
Phoebe,he wants you here. It's great. You can make yummy noises.
菲比,他也要你在場 這樣對我有好處 因為你可以發出好吃的讚歎聲
-What are you gonna make? -Yummy noises.
-你打算做什麼? -好吃的聲音.
-And Monica,what are you gonna make? -I don't know. It's gotta be great.
摩妮卡,你要做什麼菜? 我也不知道,但一定會很棒的
I know what you can make! I know!
我知道你可以做什麼了!
You should make that thing with the stuff.
你應該用那些東西做這個.
You know that thing with the stuff?
你知道用那些東西做的這個?
Okay,I don't know.
好吧,我也不知道
Anyone know a good date place in the neighborhood?
各位,誰知道附近有約會的絕佳地點?
How about Tony's? If you finish a 32-ounce steak,it's free.
東尼餐廳如何?吃下32盎斯的牛排就免費
Anyone know a good place if you're not dating a puma?
誰知道和美洲豹約會,哪兒是好地點?
-Who are you going out with? -ls this the bug lady?
-你要和誰約會? -是昆蟲女?
"I love you,Ross."
我愛你,羅斯
Her name is Celia and she's insect curator at the museum.
她叫希莉亞,不是昆蟲女 她是昆蟲博物館的主任
-What are you gonna do? -Go out to dinner...
-你們打算如何共渡? -出去吃晚餐
...then bring her back to my place and introduce her to my monkey.
然後帶她回我的住處 介紹我的猴子給她認識
And he's not speaking metaphorically.
他沒用暗示
So back to your place? You thinking maybe....
回你的住處?你想...
Well,I don't know....
我不知道…
I'm hoping....
我希望…
That monkey is a chick magnet.
告訴你,那猴子是魅力十足
She'll take one look at his cute, little face and it'll seal the deal.
她看見它那毛絨絨可愛的小臉 然後一切就搞定
Celia,don't worry. He's not gonna hurt you!
希莉亞,別擔心,它不會傷害你的
Soothing tones.
用安撫的語調
-Here,Marcel. -I can't stand this.
-過來,馬修 -我受不了了.
-He's got his claws on my -Yeah,all right.
-它的爪子在我的 -乖..
Okay,try this salmon mousse.
試試這鮭魚慕斯
Good.
好吃
Is it better than the other salmon mousse?
比其他的鮭魚慕斯好吃?
-It's creamier. -Yeah? Well,is that better?
-更滑更柔 -是嗎?這樣更好?
I don't know. We're talking about whipped fish.
我不知道.我們在談一條攪成泡沫的魚
I'm just happy I'm keeping it down.
我能不吐出來就已經不錯了
God,what happened to you?
天啊,你怎麼了?
Eight and a half hours of aptitude tests...
8個半小時的性向測驗
...intelligence tests,personality tests,and what do I learn?
智力測驗,個性測驗,我瞭解了什麼?
"You're suited for data processing for a large multinational corporation."
你適合在大型跨國公司 資料處理部門方面發展
That's so great! You already know how to do that.
這太好了 因為你已知道該如何做
Can you believe it?
你們能相信嗎?
Don't I seem like I should be doing something cool?
我不像是做那種酷工作的人嗎?
I just always pictured myself doing something....
我總是想像自己能做點事情
Something!
事情!
Chandler,I know,I know.
錢德,我知道
Hey,you can see your nipples through this shirt.
嗨,你可以透過你的襯衫 看自己的乳頭
Maybe this will cheer you up.
這個或許能讓你開心點
I had a grape about five hours ago, so I better split this with you.
5小時前我吃了一顆葡萄 所以我最好該和你平分
It's supposed to be small. It's a pre-appetizer.
它本來就應該那麼小 這是餐前開胃菜
The French call it an amuse-bouche.
法國人稱它為「阿姆茲布許」
Well,it is amusing.
這簡直是太神奇了
Hi,Wendy. Yeah,8:00.
溫蒂,對,八點
What did we say,$10 an hour?
我們不是說過嗎?每小時十塊
Okay,great. All right,I'll see you then.
很好,再見了
-$10 an hour for what? -A waitress from work is helping me.
-什麼每小時十塊? -我請餐廳裡的女服務生幫忙
Waitressing?
服務生?
Of course I thought of you. But....
當然我考慮過你.但...
-But.... -But,but....
-但是… -但是什麼?
But it's just this night has to go just perfect,you know?
但是這今晚一定要做到完美,你知道嗎?
Wendy's more of a professional waitress.
溫蒂的經驗豐富,是個職業服務生
And I'm maintaining my amateur status so I can waitress in the Olympics.
我應該繼續保持業餘的姿態 將來才能在奧運會上當服務生
I don't mean to brag,but I waited tables at lnnsbruck in '76.
我不想自吹自擂 但我在76年的因斯布魯克當過服務生
Took home a bronze.
帶回家一塊銅牌.
Amuse-bouche?
阿姆茲-布許?
Talk to me.
和我說話
A weird thing happened on the train this morning
早上我坐地鐵時 發生了一件詭異的事
Talk dirty.
說猥褻的話
-Here? -Come on. Come on.
-這裡? -對.
Say something hot.
說點火辣的
What? What?
什麼?什麼?
Vulva.
外陰.
Vulva?
外陰?
I panicked,all right? She took me by surprise.
我當時好害怕,她嚇了我一跳
But it wasn't a total loss. We ended up cuddling.
但並未完全失去自我.我們以愛撫收場
You cuddled? How many times?
愛撫?幾次?
Shut up. It was nice.
閉嘴,那種感覺好好
I don't think I'm a dirty-talking kind of guy.
我不是那種講猥褻話的人
Just say what you wanna do to her. Or what you want her to do to you.
你只要說出你想對她如何 或是你想她對你如何
Or what other people might be doing to each other.
或是別人想對彼此如何
I'll tell you what. Try something on me.
這樣吧,對我說吧
Please be kidding.
開什麼玩笑
Why not?
有何不可,
Just close your eyes and tell me what you'd like to be doing right now.
只要閉上眼睛告訴我 現在你想幹什麼
I'm in my apartment....
好吧…我在我的住處
-Yeah,what else? -You're not there.
-然後呢? -你不在那裡.
-We're not having this conversation. -All right,I'll start. Ready?
-我們在進行這樣的談話 -好的,我要開始了,準備好了嗎?
Oh,Ross...
噢,羅斯
...you get me so hot. I want your lips on me now.
你讓我慾火焚身, 我要你舔我
-Now you say something. -I really don't think so.
-該你了 -我看還是算了吧
You like this woman,right? You wanna see her again,right?
你喜歡她吧?想再見到她嗎?
If you can't talk dirty to me, how will you talk dirty to her?
如果你無法對我說出狠褻的話 你如何對她說呢?
Now tell me you wanna caress my butt!
說你想愛撫我的屁股
Okay,turn around.
好吧,轉過去
I don't want you staring at me.
我不想你盯著我看
All right,I'm not looking. Go ahead.
好吧,我不看,說吧
Okay.
Ok.
I want Okay,I want...
我要...
...to feel your hot,soft skin with my lips.
用我的雙唇感覺你那光滑的皮膚
There you go. IKeep going,keep going.
這就對了,繼續
I want to take my tongue and
我要用我的舌頭…
Say it.
快說啊
Say it!
快說
run it all over your body...
舔遍你的全身
... until you're trembling with
直到你顫抖…
With?
然後呢?
-Funny story. -You're not gonna believe this.
-真好笑 -你不會相信的
I was always rooting for you two kids to get together.
我一向贊成你們兩個小子交往
-The trembling thing was nice. -Shut up!
-顫抖那一段不錯 -閉嘴!
That guy from your old job called again.
你睡覺時老東家又打電話來
-Again? -And again and again and again.
-又打來? -一遍又一遍.
And again.
又打來了
Hey,Mr. Costilick. How's life on the 1 5th floor?
科先生,15樓的情況如何?
Yeah,I miss you too.
我也想念你.
It's a lot less satisfying to steal pens from your own home.
對,偷家裡的筆不夠刺激
That's very generous. But this isn't about the money.
你真慷慨,但這不是錢的問題
I need more than a job. I need something I really care ab
我需要的不只是一份工作 我要的是我真正想要的
That's on top of the year-end bonus?
這是你稍早提過的年終紅利之外的津貼?
Your dream!
你的夢想…
Look,Al,I'm not playing hardball here,okay?
艾爾,我不是在故意為難你
This is not a negotiation. This is a rejection!
這不是交涉,這叫拒絕
Stop saying numbers!
不,別再講數字了
I'm telling you, you've got the wrong guy!
告訴你,你看錯人了
I'll see you Monday!
星期一見
Wow! It's huge! It's so much bigger than the cubicle.
好大,比小格子大多了
This is a cube!
這是一個格間!
Look at this.
看這裡.
You have a window!
你有窗戶!
Yes,indeed-y. With a beautiful view of
沒錯,還有美麗的風…
Look! That guy's peeing!
看,有人在小便
That's enough of the view. Check this out.
風景看夠了,看這個
Okay,sit down here.
坐下
This is great.
這個最酷,
-You ready? -Yeah.
-準備好沒? -好了
Helen,could you come in here?
海倫,能進來一下嗎?
Thank you,Helen. That'll be all.
謝謝你,海倫,沒事了
Last time I do that. I promise.
最後一次了,我保證
-She doesn't seem very warm. -I know. She has no personality.
-她看起來不怎麼熱情 -我知道.她沒有個性.
Wendy,don't do this to me.
溫蒂,不要這樣對我.
We had a deal. Yeah,you promised.
我們約好的.你答應過我
-Who was that? -Wendy bailed.
-那是誰? -叛徒溫蒂
I have no waitress.
我沒服務生了
That's too bad. Bye-bye.
真是太糟糕了.再見
Ten dollars an hour! Twelve dollars an hour!
一小時十元!一小時十二元!
I wish I could,but I've made plans to walk around.
我希望可以 但我已經計劃好去走走
When you ran out on your wedding, I was there.
你逃婚之後我一直關心你
I put a roof over your head! If that means nothing....
我讓你有地方住 如果這樣對你仍毫無意義…
Twenty dollars an hour.
一小時二十元
Done.
成交
Hello. Welcome to Monica's. May I take your coat?
歡迎光臨摩尼卡的廚房 我能拿你的外套嗎?
-Hi,Steve. -Hello,Monica.
-史帝夫 -摩妮卡
Hello,greeter girl.
招待小姐
-This is Rachel. -Yeah,okay.
-她叫瑞秋 -好的,
Everything smells so delicious.
味道好香
I can't remember ever smelling such a delicious combination of
我早已忘記這種…
Okay,smells.
香味
-It's a lovely apartment. -Thank you. Would you like a tour?
-這房子真漂亮 -謝謝,想參觀一下嗎?
I was just being polite, but all right.
我只是客套一下,但,好吧
-What's up? -ln the cab on the way over...
-怎麼了? -他坐計程車來時
...Steve blazed up a doobie.
燃了一根草
What?
什麼?
Smoked a joint,you know? Lit a bone. Weed,hemp,ganja
抽了一根大麻… 好了,我懂
I'm with you,Cheech.
我和你在一起,cheech.
-Do you think he's gonna be cool? -ls it dry in here?
-你認為他會冷靜嗎? -這裡很乾燥嗎?
Let me get you some wine.
我來為你倒杯酒
I think we're ready for our first course too.
我們可以上第一道菜了
These are rock shrimp ravioli in a cilantro ponzu sauce...
這些是石蝦小方餃
...with just a touch of minced...
芫萎調味醬加上一點點…
...ginger.
碎姜
Well,smack my ass and call me Judy!
打我屁股叫我朱蒂
-These are fantastic! -Gosh! I'm so glad you liked them.
-真是太好吃了 -我真高興你喜歡
Like them? I could eat 100 of them!
喜歡?我可以吃下上百個
That's all there is of these...
只有這一些
...but in a few minutes, we'll serve some tartlets.
但再過8分半鍾 我們就會獻上美味的洋蔥餡餅
"Tartlets"?
餡餅...
"Tartlets."
Word has lost all meaning.
文字都已失去意義
Excuse me. Can I help you with anything?
請問需要任何幫忙嗎?
You know,I don't know what I'm looking for.
你看,我也不知道自己在找什麼
Cool! Taco shells!
酷,墨西哥餡餅
They're like a little corn envelope,you know?
這個就像是玉米卷
-You don't wanna spoil your appetite. -Hey,Sugar-O's!
-你不該影響食慾. -糖歐
You know,if you just wait another 6 1 /2 minutes
再等6分鐘半
Macaroni and cheese! We gotta make this!
乾酪通心面!我們要做這個
-No,we don't. -Oh,okay.
-不,我們不做 -哦,好吧.
Sorry.
抱歉
Why don't you just have a seat here?
我們何不坐這兒
-Give me the gummy bears. -No.
-小熊軟糖給我 -不
-Give them to me. -We'll share.
-把他給我 -好吧,分你一半
-No. Give me the bears. -You can't have any.
-小熊給我 -你不能全部搶走
It's not worth it!
這樣不值得!
Bears overboard! They're drowning!
小熊落水了,他們快淹死了
Don't just stand there. Call 9-1 -1.
不要站在那裡.打9-1-1.
Hey,fellas,grab onto a Sugar-O! Save yourselves!
嗨,夥計們,抓住糖歐逃命啊!
Help! Help,I'm drowning!
救命啊....我淹水了
-That's it! Dinner is over! -What! Why?
-我受夠了,晚餐結束 -什麼?為什麼?
Why? What if I came into your office and I started...?
什麼?試想一下我到你的辦公室然後開始...?
I can't think of an example.
我想不出一個合適的例子.
I've waited seven years for an opportunity like this...
這機會我已等了七年
...and you can't wait 4 1 /2 minutes for a tartlet?
而你卻等不了四分半鍾之後 再吃洋蔥餡餅
So I told him, "I'm sorry. That's how I feel."
所以我跟他說, "對不起.這就是我的感受."
And he told me I harsh-ed his buzz.
他居然說我聲音太刺耳搞得他耳朵嗡嗡叫
Then I said,"Don't eat that. It's a kitchen magnet."
然後我說,"別吃這個,這是廚房磁鐵"
And he didn't listen, so we left him in the emergency room.
結果他不聽,我們只好把他留在急救室了.
-Mon,I'm sorry. -What a tool.
-摩尼卡,對不起 -真是個王八蛋
-You did the right thing. -You don't wanna work for that guy.
-你做的很對 -你不會想為那種人工作的
I just thought that this was it.
我以為我的機會來了
-Don't worry. You're an amazing chef. -Those yummy noises? I wasn't faking.
-不要擔心.你是個了不起的廚師 -記得那些讚美的聲音?我不是裝的
Am I gonna get paid for the full three hours?
我能拿到全時三小時工資嗎?
Just a question. We'll talk about it later.
只是一個問題而已.我們以後再說.
So,how did it go with Celia?
和希莉亞的狀況如何?
-I was unbelievable. -All right,Ross!
-我簡直是太神了 -幹得好,羅斯!
I was the James Michener of dirty talk.
我就像是詹姆斯密奇尼一樣滿口狠褻的話
It was the most elaborate filth ever heard.
天下最具巧思的猥褻話
I mean,there were characters, plot lines,themes,a motif.
有人物,劇情,主題
At one point,there were villagers.
其中一段的主角是村夫與村姑
And?
然後呢?
By the time we finished all the dirty talk...
猥褻話講完後已經很晚了
...it was late and we were exhausted
而且我們也已精疲力竭所以…
-You cuddled. -Yeah,which was nice.
-你們愛撫? -那種感覺好好
Do you guys want to try to catch a late movie?
你們想看晚場電影嗎?
-Shouldn't we wait for Chandler? -Where the hell is he?
-或許吧,但我們不是該等錢德? -他到底跑哪兒去了?
I know what time it is...
我知道現在幾點
...but I'm looking at the WENUS and I'm not happy!
但我看著WENUS而且我相當不高興
Let me tell you something.
真的?告訴你吧
You will care about it because I care about it. Got it? Good!
你會在乎是因為我在乎,明白了嗎?很好!
How's this?
這樣如何?
Sorry. How about over here?
不好意思,這邊那?
That means it's working.
這就說明有效果了.
-Does this hurt? -No.
-痛不痛? -不痛.
How about this?
這樣呢?
There you go!
爽啦!
I'm gonna throw up!
爽呆了!!